Her dream. Her terms.
Honey is a music, drama, romance film directed by Bille Woodruff.
Honey Daniels dreams of making a name for herself as a hip-hop choreographer.
When she's not busy hitting downtown clubs with her friends, she teaches dance classes at a
nearby community center in Harlem, N.Y., as a way to keep kids off the streets.
Honey thinks she's hit the jackpot when she meets a hotshot
director casts her in one of his music videos.
But, when he starts demanding sexual favors from her, Honey
makes a decision that will change her life.
Honey Daniels, played by Jessica Alba.
Chaz, played by Mekhi Phifer.
Benny (as Lil' Romeo), played by Romeo.
Gina, played by Joy Bryant.
Michael Ellis, played by David Moscow.
Mrs. Daniels, played by Lonette McKee.
Honey is a 2003 American dance film directed by Billie Woodruff.
It stars Jessica Alba, Mekhi Phifer, Romeo Miller, Joy Bryant, and David Moscow, with a cameo by Missy
Elliott and featured performances by Tweet, Sheek Louch, Jadakiss, Ginuwine, and Blaque.
The film explores themes of career, new york city, dancing, dance, dreams.
The tone is emotional.